Register of the Russia. Posol'stvo (U.S.) Records, 1897-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- Financial Agent Office File, 1917-1935.
  - General (Box 105)
    - Day file
      - 1925
        - October-November (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 149
        - December (Folder 7)
      - 1926
        - January (Folder 8)
        - February (Box 122, Folder 1)
        - February-March (Folder 2)
        - April (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 150
        - May (Folder 4)
        - June (Folder 5)
        - June-July (Folder 6)
        - July-August (Folder 7)
        - September-October (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 151
        - November-December (Box 123, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1927
        - January-February (Folder 3)
        - February-March (Folder 4)
        - April-May (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 152
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June-August (Folder 7)
        - August (Folder 8)
        - September-October (Folder 9)
        - October-November (Folder 10)
          Available on microfilm reel 153
        - December (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - 1928
        - January-February (Folder 2)
        - March-April (Folder 3)
        - April-May (Folder 4)
        - June-August (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 154
        - September-October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
        - December (Folder 8)
      - 1929 (Box 125)
        - January-February (Folder 1)
        - March-April (Folder 2)
          Available on microfilm reel 155
        - May-June (Folder 3)
        - July-September (Folder 4)
        - October-December (Folder 5)
      - 1930
        - January-March (Folder 6)
        - April-May (Folder 7)
        - May-August (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 156
        - August-October (Box 126, Folder 1)
        - November-December (Folder 2)
      - 1931
        - January-February (Folder 3)
        - March-April (Folder 4)
        - May-June (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 157
        - July-October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
        - December (Folder 8)
    - Report (Box 127)
      - Table of contents (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 158
      - 1917-1920
        - Explanatory note
          - Volume 1 (Folder 2-3)
          - Volume 2 (Box 128, Folder 1-2)
            Available on microfilm reel 159
          - Volume 3 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
            Available on microfilm reel 160
          - Volume 4 (Box 130, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 161
          - Volume 4 (Box 131, Folder 1)
        - Appendices (Box 132)
          - "Al'bom obraztsov denezhnykh znakov, kreditnykh biletov, obiazatel'stv gosudarstvennogo kaznacheistva i biletov vyigryshnogo zaima, izgotovlennogo po zakazam Rossiiskogo pravitel'stva" (Folder 1-2)
            Available on microfilm reel 162
          - "The National-Bank Act as Amended; the Federal Reserve Act; and other Laws Relating to National Banks," Washington: Government Printing Office, 1920 (Folder 3-4)
      - 1920-1921 -- explanatory note (Box 133)
        - Volume 1 (Folder 1-2)
          Available on microfilm reel 163
        - Volume 2 (Box 134, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 164
        - Volume 2 (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Volume 3 (Box 136, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 165
        - Volume 3 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - American Bank Note Company
    - 1920 (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 166
    - 1924 (Folder 3)
    - 1926-1927 (Folder 4)
  - American Relief Administration
    - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
    - 1921-1922 (Folder 6)
    - 1922 (Box 138)
      - February-March (Folder 1)
      - February-April (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 167
      - May-December (Folder 3)
  - American Red Cross--see Refugees, Russian/Organizations Russian Red Cross
  - Banks
    - General (Folder 4)
    - National City Bank of New York
      - General
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 5)
        - 1921-1925 (Folder 6)
      - Kidder, Peabody & Company, New York (Folder 7)
  - Brazol', Boris--see Claims/General/Private/1931-1933
  - Building maintenance. (see also Real estate management; and Russian Embassy/Building maintenance) (Folder 8-9)
  - China--see Skerst, A. G., "Money market in Manchuria"
  - Chinese Eastern Railway Company. (see also Washington Conference, 1921-1922)
    - 1922 (Folder 10)
    - 1922-1924 (Folder 11)
    - 1923 (Folder 12)
      Available on microfilm reel 168
    - 1923-1924 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - 1924 (Folder 2)
    - 1924-1926 (Folder 3)
  - Cipher keys (Folder 4)
  - Claims
    - General
      - Organizations
        - 1920 (Folder 5)
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 169
        - 1923-1925 (Folder 7)
        - 1924-1927 (Folder 8)
      - Private
        - 1930-1931 (Folder 9)
        - 1931-1932 (Folder 10)
        - 1932-1935 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Aktsionernoe obshchestvo dlia mekhanicheskoi obrabotki dereva (Folder 2)
      Available on microfilm reel 170
    - Allied Machinery Company--see American Steel Export Company
    - American Steel Export Company (Folder 3)
    - Bankers Trust Company
      - Helferish Sadet Company (Folder 4)
      - Irving National Bank--see National City Bank of New York
      - National City Bank of New York
        - 1920-1925 (Folder 5)
        - 1925-1930 (Folder 6)
        - 1930-1934 (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 171
    - Berg, Sergei (Folder 8)
    - Buniatian versus Optorg (Folder 9)
    - Bush Terminal Company (Folder 10)
    - Claude M. Nankivel and John MacGregor Grant, Inc.
      - All-Russian Zemstvos and Cities Union (Folder 11)
      - Omsk All-Russian Government (Box 141)
        - 1922
          - April-August (Folder 1)
          - August-December (Folder 2)
            Available on microfilm reel 172
        - 1922-1923 (Folder 3)
    - Driggs Ordnance Company and Globe Indemnity Company (Folder 4)
    - Erb, Newman (Folder 5)
    - Freighters
      - Anna Sophie (Folder 6)
      - Carolyn
        - 1921-1923 (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 173
        - 1923 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Frederick (Folder 2)
      - Homestead (Folder 3)
      - Rodgai
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 4)
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 5)
        - 1922-1926 (Folder 6)
        - 1926 (Folder 7)
      - Trumf (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 174
    - Gardner, E. and D. B., Petrograd (Folder 9)
    - Gaston, Williams & Wigmore, Inc.
      - 1925-1927 (Folder 10)
      - 1927-1928 (Folder 11)
      - 1928-1935 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Globe and Rodgers Fire Insurance Company--see Claude M. Nankival and John MacGregor Grant, Inc./All-Russian Zemstvos and Cities Union
    - Globe Indemnity Company--see Driggs Ordnance Company
    - Gold
      - 1928-1929 (Folder 2)
      - 1929-1932 (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 175
    - Great Britain, Government of
      - Freight charges (Folder 4)
      - Seizure of the Russian cargo by the
        - General
          - 1920-1922 (Folder 5-6)
          - 1923-1926 (Folder 7)
        - Abo Jermanufaktur Och Waggonfabrik, Finland (Box 144, Folder 1)
        - Berg, Abraham (Folder 2)
        - Davies Turner Company--see Treugol'nik, Russian-American India Rubber Company
        - Elworthy, R. & T., Ltd. (Folder 3)
        - General Electric Company (Folder 4)
        - Ingersol Rand Company (Folder 5)
        - Iznosskov i kompaniia (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 176
        - John MacGregor Grant, Inc., New York (Folder 7)
        - Kymmene Aktienblag of Finland (Folder 8)
        - National City Bank of New York--see Russo- Baltic Car Works
        - Renault Selling Branch, Inc., New York (Folder 9)
        - Russo-Baltic Car Works (Folder 10)
        - Treugol'nik, Russian-American India Rubber Company (Folder 11)
        - United States Government (Folder 12)
        - Worthington Pump and Machinery Corporation (Folder 13)
    - Great Northern Railway Company (Folder 14)
    - Jenssen, Bergithon (Folder 15)
    - Korf, Oskar (Folder 16)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company (Box 145)
      - 1922-1923 (Folder 1)
      - 1923-1924 (Folder 2)
      - 1924-1925 (Folder 3)
      - 1925-1927 (Folder 4)
        Available on microfilm reel 177
      - 1927 (Folder 5)
      - 1928-1934 (Folder 6)
    - Morton Truck and Tractor Company (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Moscow Machine Tool Company (Folder 2)
    - New York Central Railroad Company (Folder 3)
    - Northern Pacific Railroad Company, Seattle
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 4)
      - 1920-1922 (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 178
    - Optorg, Soviet trade organization--see Buniatian versus Optorg
    - Paterson, New Jersey (Folder 6)
    - People's Industrial Trading Corporatin, New York (Folder 7)
    - Ronis versus Ustinov (Folder 8)
    - Russian-American Agricultural Company--see Aktsionernoe obshchestvo obrabotki dereva
    - Russian insurance companies
      - 1924-1928 (Folder 9)
      - 1928-1929 (Folder 10)
      - 1929-1935 (Folder 11)
    - Russian Volunteer Fleet (Box 147)
      - General (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 179
      - Great Britain, Government of--see United States Government
      - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, Government of the
        - 1921-1925 (Folder 2)
        - 1923 (Folder 3)
      - United States Government
        - General
          - 1920-1922 (Folder 4)
          - 1927-1930 (Folder 5)
          - 1930-1931 (Folder 6)
            Available on microfilm reel 180
          - 1931 (Box 148)
            - June-July (Folder 1)
            - July-September (Folder 2)
            - September-November (Folder 3)
            - November-December (Folder 4)
          - 1931-1932 (Folder 5)
            Available on microfilm reel 181
          - 1932
            - January-February (Folder 6)
            - February-April (Folder 7)
            - May (Folder 8)
            - May-June (Box 149, Folder 1)
            - July-September (Folder 2)
          - 1932-1933 (Folder 3)
          - 1933-1935 (Folder 4)
            Available on microfilm reel 182
        - Massilou Bridge (Folder 5)
        - Smoke boxes (Folder 6)
        - Standard Shipbuilding Corporation
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 7)
          - 1921-1922 (Folder 8)
    - Tomasheva, Elizaveta (Folder 9)
    - Turney Transportation Company (Folder 10)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics--see Buniatian versus Optorg; Gold; and Lehigh Valley Railroad Company
    - United States--see Tomasheva, Elizaveta; and Vyksunska Metallurgical and Mechanical Company
    - Ustinov--see Ronis versus Ustinov
    - Vyksunska Metallurgical and Mechanical Company (Box 150)
      - 1929-1932 (Folder 1)
      - 1932
        - February-May (Folder 2)
          Available on microfilm reel 183
        - May-September (Folder 3)
      - 1932-1933 (Folder 4)
      - 1933-1938 (Folder 5)
  - Commercial products
    - General
      - 1920-1922 (Folder 6)
      - 1921 (Folder 7)
      - 1922 (Box 151, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 184
      - 1923
        - January-July (Folder 2)
        - July-December (Folder 3)
      - 1924-1927 (Folder 4)
    - Books--see Microscopes and books
    - Cartridges
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
      - 1923 (Folder 6)
      - 1923-1925 (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 185
      - 1926 (Folder 8)
    - Coal (Folder 9)
    - Freight cars (Box 152)
      - 1924 (Folder 1)
      - 1925 (Folder 2)
      - 1926 (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 186
      - 1926-1927 (Folder 4)
    - Fuses--see Cartridges
    - Locomotives
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
      - 1921-1926 (Folder 6)
      - 1926 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - 1926-1927 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 187
    - Microscopes and books (Folder 3)
    - Military shoes
      - 1920 (Folder 4)
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
      - 1921-1922 (Folder 6)
    - Rails (Folder 7)
    - Rifles (Folder 8)
      Available on microfilm reel 188
    - Steam hoists (Folder 9)
    - Steel (Folder 10)
    - Warehouses
      - Astor Warehouse, New York (Folder 11)
      - Bush Terminal Company--see Seifert, L. F.'s Sons, Inc.
      - East Waterway Dock and Warehouse Company, Seattle (Folder 12)
      - Independent Stores, New York--see Seifert, L. F.'s Sons, Inc.
      - Isdahl and Company, Bergen, Norway (Folder 13)
      - Jarvis Stores, Inc., New York (Folder 14)
      - Merchants Warehouse Company. (see also Seifert, L.F.'s Sons, Inc.) (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Pioneer Fireproof Storage Warehouses
        - 1920-1926 (Folder 2)
        - 1921-1924 (Folder 3)
      - Seifert, L. F.'s Sons, Inc. (Folder 4)
      - Terry, W. M. Company, Bridgeport, Connecticut
        - 1920
          - List of products (Folder 5)
          - Receipts (Folder 6)
        - 1921
          - Correspondence
            - January-May (Folder 7)
            - February-July (Folder 8)
          - Receipts (Folder 9)
        - 1924-1926 (Folder 10)
      - Vandal Warehouse Company, New York--see Jarvis Stores, Inc., New York
    - Wheel pairs (Folder 11)
  - Commission for Reviewing Petitions for Assistance (Folder 12)
  - Composition and structure
    - General
      - 1920 (Folder 13)
      - 1920-1922 (Folder 14)
      - 1920-1923 (Folder 15)
    - Budget (Folder 16)
    - Diplomatic mail pouch (Folder 17)
    - Employees
      - General (Folder 18)
      - Berg, L. S. (Folder 19)
      - Karpin, S.--see Podtiagin, Viktor
      - Podtiagin, Viktor (Folder 20)
      - Sergievskaia, Elena (Folder 21)
  - Division of Supplies -- "Otchet o deiatel'nosti Otdela po snabzheniiu pri Rossiiskom posol'stve v Vashingtone." (see also Pertsov, Dmitrii/Division of Supplies) (Box 155)
    - General
      - Correspondence (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 189
      - Notes (Folder 2)
      - Notes and draft copies (Folder 3-4)
    - 1918-1919
      - Draft copy (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 190
      - Draft copy (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Mimeographed copy (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Mimeographed copy (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - Mimeographed copy (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 1919-1920 -- explanatory note (Box 160)
      - Volume 1 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 191
      - Volume 1 (Box 161, Folder 1)
      - Volume 1 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Volume 2 (Box 163, Folder 1-2)
        Available on microfilm reel 192
      - Volume 2 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Volume 3 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 193
      - Volume 3 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
  - Eddystone Ammunition Corporation (Box 166, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 194
  - European War, 1914-1918
    - "Sbornik zapisok, otnosiashchikhsia k russkomu snabzheniiu v Velikuiu voinu"
      - Clippings, correspondence, notes, typewritten copies of some chapters
        - 1923-1924 (Folder 2)
        - 1924-1925 (Folder 3)
        - 1925 (Folder 4)
        - 1925-1926 (Folder 5)
        - 1926 (Folder 6)
      - Mimeographed copies (Box 167, Folder 1-2)
        Available on microfilm reel 195
    - Supply agencies in belligirent countries--see "Sbornik zapisok, otnosiashchikhsia k russkomu snabzheniiu v Velikuiu voinu"
  - Finance. (see also Banks; Pertsov, Dmitrii; and Skerst, A. G., "Money market in Manchuria") (Box 168)
    - General
      - General
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 1)
        - 1920-1924 (Folder 2)
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 3-4)
          Available on microfilm reels 195 and 196
        - 1922 (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 196
        - 1923 (Folder 6)
        - 1923-1924 (Folder 7)
        - 1924-1925 (Folder 8)
        - 1925 (Folder 9)
        - 1926-1927 (Folder 10)
      - Cash books (Box 169)
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 197
        - 1921 (Folder 2)
        - 1922
          - Main (Folder 3)
          - Auxiliary (Folder 4)
      - Reports (Box 170)
        - 1926 (Folder 1)
        - 1927 (Folder 2)
    - Accounts
      - General
        - Checkstubs (Folder 3)
        - Statements (Folder 4)
      - Fonds (Folder 5)
      - Transfers
        - Checkstubs
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 6)
          - 1921 (Box 171, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 198
          - 1922
            - January (Folder 2)
            - May-July (Folder 3)
            - August-September (Folder 4)
        - Payment files
          - 1921 (Folder 5)
          - 1922
            - January (Folder 6)
            - July-October (Folder 7)
          - 1925 (Folder 8)
        - Receiving files
          - 1924 (Folder 9)
          - 1926 (Folder 10)
      - Uget, S. A., Special (Box 172)
        - Checkstubs
          - 1920 (Folder 1)
          - 1921
            - February-August (Folder 2)
            - July (Folder 3)
            - August-September (Folder 4)
        - Receiving files (Folder 5)
    - Financial management
      - 1921
        - May-June (Folder 6)
        - June-October (Folder 7)
        - October-December (Box 173, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 199
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1922
        - January-February (Folder 3)
        - February-March (Folder 4)
        - March-May (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June-August (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 200
      - 1923
        - March-April (Folder 8)
        - May-June (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - 1927-1928 (Folder 2)
      - 1928 (Folder 3)
      - 1928-1929 (Folder 4)
      - 1929
        - February-May (Folder 5)
        - May-December (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 201
      - 1930
        - January-February (Folder 7)
        - March-June (Folder 8)
        - June-November (Folder 9)
      - 1932 (Folder 10)
      - 1933 (Box 175)
        - January-March (Folder 1)
        - April-May (Folder 2)
          Available on microfilm reel 202
        - May-June (Folder 3)
        - July-August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - September-October (Folder 6)
        - October-November (Box 176, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 203
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1934
        - January (Folder 4)
        - January-February (Folder 5)
        - February-March (Folder 6)
        - March (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 204
        - April (Box 177, Folder 1)
        - April-May (Folder 2)
        - May-June (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
  - Freighters
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Eastern Victor. (see also Supervisory staff)
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 6)
        Available on microfilm reel 205
      - 1920-1922 (Folder 7)
    - Faraby. (see also Eastern Victor and Supervisory staff) (Folder 8)
    - Hog Island. (see also Eastern Victor) (Box 178)
      - 1920 (Folder 1)
      - 1290-1921 (Folder 2)
    - Jason (Folder 3)
    - Melrose--see Wisconsin Bridge
    - Nizhnii Novgorod (Folder 4)
    - Omsk
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
      - 1921 (Folder 6)
    - Pawnee--see Sangamon
    - Sangamon (Folder 7-8)
      Available on microfilm reel 206
    - Supervisory staff (Folder 9)
    - Wisconsin Bridge (Folder 10)
  - Germany (Box 179)
    - Economic conditions--see Russian Information Bureau
    - Reichsrat. Bulletins
      - 1925 (Folder 1)
      - 1926
        - January-February (Folder 2)
        - March-June (Folder 3)
        - July-October (Folder 4)
          Available on microfilm reel 207
        - November-December (Folder 5)
      - 1927 (Folder 6)
  - Germonius, Eduard. (see also Claims/General/Private/1931- 1932) (Folder 7)
  - Herperman, Henry--see Commerical products/Locomotives
  - Holmes Electric Protective Company--see Building maintenance
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace--see World politics/1926-1927
  - Iznosskov i kompaniia--see Claims/General/Private/1931-1932
  - Kokovtsev, Count--see Claims/General/Private/1931-1932
  - Lukomskii, General--see Freighters/Omsk
  - Military Agent (Box 180)
    - 1920 (Folder 1)
    - 1921
      - January (Folder 2)
      - February-March (Folder 3)
  - Naval Agent
    - 1920 (Folder 4)
    - 1921 (Folder 5)
  - New York Telephone Company
    - 1920 (Folder 6)
    - 1921 (Folder 7)
  - Novitskii, Vladimir (Folder 8)
  - Office supply
    - 1920-1921 (Folder 9-10)
    - 1921 (Folder 11)
    - 1921-1930 (Folder 12)
      Available on microfilm reel 208
    - 1923-1930 (Folder 13)
    - 1924 (Folder 14)
    - 1927 (Folder 15)
  - Pavlovskii, Iu. A., "Russkii gosudarstvennyi dolg," Russkii ekonomist, 1, n.d. Synopsis (Folder 16)
  - Pertsov, Dmitrii
    - General. Reports
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 17)
      - 1921-1924 (Folder 18)
      - 1924-1925 (Folder 19)
    - Division of Supplies. Report (Box 181, Folder 1-2)
      Available on microfilm reel 209
    - Financial Agent
      - General
        - Memorandum (Folder 3)
        - Reports
          - 1920
            - January-April (Folder 4)
            - April-November (Folder 5-6)
              Folder 5 available on microfilm reel 209 and folder 6 on reel 210
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 7)
            Available on microfilm reel 210
          - 1923-1925 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Claims (Folder 2)
      - Loans to Omsk All-Russian Government (Folder 3)
      - London and Eastern Trade Bank (Folder 4)
  - Petrograd Zemstvos and Cities Regional Committee. (see also Commercial products/Locomotives) (Folder 5)
  - Real Estate management. (see also Russian Embassy, Washington)
    - 1921-1926 (Folder 6)
    - 1927-1933 (Folder 7)
  - Refugees, Russian. (see also Claims/General/Private; Claims/Russian insurance companies; Finance/Accounts/ Transfers/Payment files and Receiving files; Finance/ Accounts/Uget, S. A., Special/Receiving files; Russian church; Russian Embassy, Washington; Russian Information Bureau; and World economic conditions)
    - General
      - Correspondence
        - 1923-1927 (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 211
        - 1928-1933 (Folder 9)
      - Inquiries
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 10)
        - 1921-1922 (Folder 11)
        - 1922-1923 (Box 183, Folder 1)
        - 1924-1925 (Folder 2)
        - 1925-1930 (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 212
        - 1930-1935 (Folder 4)
    - Canada--see Far East
    - Eastern Europe and Turkey
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 5)
      - 1920-1923 (Folder 6)
      - 1923 (Folder 7)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - 1924-1925 (Folder 2)
        Available on microfilm reel 213
      - 1925-1926 (Folder 3)
      - 1926-1931 (Folder 4)
    - Far East
      - 1922-1923 (Folder 5)
      - 1923
        - February-April (Folder 6)
        - April-July (Box 185, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 214
        - July-August (Folder 2)
        - August-Septmber (Folder 3)
        - September-November (Folder 4)
        - December (Folder 5)
      - 1924
        - January-April (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 215
        - April-May (Folder 7)
        - June (Box 186, Folder 1)
        - July-October (Folder 2)
      - 1924-1925 (Folder 3)
      - 1925
        - February-March (Folder 4)
          Available on microfilm reel 216
        - March-November (Folder 5)
      - 1925-1926 (Folder 6)
      - 1926
        - February-June (Folder 7)
        - June-December (Folder 8)
      - 1927-1933 (Box 187, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 217
    - Inheritance
      - General
        - 1926-1928 (Folder 2)
        - 1928-1933 (Folder 3)
      - Tsorn, Mikhail, Captain (Folder 4)
    - Organizations
      - General
        - 1927-1929 (Folder 5)
        - 1929-1930 (Folder 6)
          Available on microfilm reel 218
        - 1930-1933 (Folder 7)
      - Association of Russian Finance Ministry Employees (Box 188)
        - Bulletins